Guide to the Phillip C. Keenan Papers, 1925-1999 RG.40.186
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.1995.0166, 1925-1999; 9.6 Cubic feet; (8) cartons
  - Mira Variables, 1925-1987
    - Early Mira Variables – Luminosities, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Early-Type Stars Infrared Wavelengths, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Early Type Stars – Line Profiles, 1953 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Green Bands in M-Type Stars, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - HD 191980 B p(Wk, He), 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - HD 191980 Bp, 1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - High Velocity SR+ Variables – D- Lines, 1963-1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Infra-Red Spectrum of VV Cephei, 1945-1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Infrared Spectra – Im Region M, S, Stars, 1964-1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Infrared Stars, 1966 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Identification of ACO Band λ4842 Mira, RR Boo, R Vir, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Interstellar D-Lines – Wavelengths (Comparison Stars), 1958-1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Long Period Variables-Proper Motions, 1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M7, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M Cep – Infrared, 1946 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M-Dwarfs – Boeshaar, 1976 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M-Type Slow Novae, 1963-1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M-Type Stars – Enlargements of PB Infrared Spectra, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M-Type Stars GB Infrared Wavelengths, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M Variables, 1942-1975 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - M Variables – Maser Stars, 1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Metallic – Line Stars, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira, 1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira II, 1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables - λ 4840 Region A10 Bands, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables in Clusters, 1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – D Lines, 1959-1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Enlargements in Blue, 1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Enlargements of Coude' Plates, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Molecular Bands Vistas w Astronomy, 1966-1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Luminosities from Motions, 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Reports and Talks, 1961-1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Mira Variables – Reports, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Model Atmospheres – Red Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - NOVAE, 1939 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Peculiar A-Type Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Possible M Subgiants, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Prints of HD 191980, 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - R Hya – Mt. Wilson Wavelengths, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - R Leonis, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - R SER, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Regular Red Variables, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - RT Cyg, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Semiregular and Irregular Variables, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Small Amplitude Red Variables – 17 γ4 Ser, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Small Amplitude Variables, 1956-1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Small-Amplitude Variables Classification, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Small-Amplitude Variables-Luminosities, 1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Spectral Classification – Early Types, 1963-1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - SR Variables – High Velocity, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Sra Variables – Light Curves, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - SR-M Intermediate Variables, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - SRM (SRa) Variables, 1962-1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Stars Similar to VV CeP, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Tc in Late-Type Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Band Intensities, 1973 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification (2 folders), 1978 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification by Band Intensities, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification by Lines on Coude Spectograms, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification – Correspondence, 1967-1987 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification in Orange, 1987 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Classification – Mt. Wilson, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Colors, 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Dwarfs, 1972-1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Enlargements in Visual and Blue Regions, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Enlargements of Grating Infrared Spectra, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – High Velocity Stars, 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Maser Bands, 1980 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Narrow Band Photometry, 1966-1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Standards, 1951-1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Temperatures, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Types of Faint Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – Variable Balmer Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – VO and TiO Bands in λ5700-5800 Region, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M – VO Bands, 1960-1966 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Type M Wavelengths – Identifications, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Types B-A Peculiar Spectra, 1964-1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Types K-M – Lithium 6708, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Types M & S – YO λ6132 Band, 1965-1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - U Ori, 1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Variable Stars – RV Tauri Stars, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Variable Stars – Semiregular – Project 12733 250, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Variable Stars – Short Period Chepheids, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - VV Cep – Oxygen Lines, 1944-1966 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - VV Cephei – Blue and Visual Regions, 1958 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - VV Cephei, 1957-1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - VY Cma, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - W and, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Z Oph, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Z Oph Radial Velocity, 1958 (Box UA.1995.0166.0005)
    - Cordoba Papers, 1966-1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Deutsch – Keenan; Project; MDK Paper, 1962-1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Early Long-Period Emission Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Early Long-Period Variables Estimated Line Intensities, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Luminosities from Interstellar Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Metal Abundancies in Mira Variables, 1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables, 1925-1928 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – A10, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – A10 – KDG Paper, 1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Atomic Lines, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables Classification Small Scale, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Colors, 1964-1966 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Comparison Stars, 1961-1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Distribution, 1953 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables Garrison's Data, 1962-1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables - Hα Emission, 1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Infrared Bands, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Lick Data, 1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Light Curves, 1951 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Line Weakening, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Magnitudes, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Me, Se – Variations with Phase Zro/Tio, 1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Measured Line Intensities, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Model Atmospheres, 1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Molecular Bands, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Morris Manuscript, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Observing Lists, 1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Old MW Plates, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Revised Catalogue, 1969-1975 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Shock Waves, 1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – South Africa, 1966-1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Spectral Luminosity Criteria, 1956-1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Spectral Statistics, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Spectral Types, 1978 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables – Statistics of Light Curves, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Mira Variables with Double Maxima, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Project RF 1110 Mira Variables, 1961-1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Project Rf 2252 – Mira Variables, 1964-1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - RF Project 823 (over) – Early Long-Period Variables Coude Spectograms D- Line Project, 1957-1958 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - RF Project 1678 Mira Variables – Selected Group, 1963-1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Short Long Period Variables – Field Charts, 1964-1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Southern Mira Variables – Field Charts, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Southern Mira Variables – Spectra, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Spinrod, 1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Suspected Variable Stars, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - SX and Comparison Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars- Distribution, 1948 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars – IAU Commission 27, 1957-1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars – IAU Subcommission on Spectra, undated, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars, 1953–1958 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars Magnitudes, 1963, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variable Stars – Spectrophotometry, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variables – Galactic Nucleus, 1958 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - Variables Stars – Field Charts, 1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
    - VO Project: Iwanowska, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0006)
  - Minor Research Files, 1931-1995
    - 2.1 Meter White Spectograph, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - 32- inch spectrograph – slit, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - 42" Flagstaff Telescope- Coude', 1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - All-Mirror Spectograph (Yoder), 1960-1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Aluminization, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Am Spectograph for 72", 1969-1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Arizona, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Arizona Project, 1953 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Asteroids, 1978 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Archives – Data Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Data Centers, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Instruments – Small Telescopes, 1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Names – Spelling, Pronunciation, 1942 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Statistics, 1966, 1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Tables, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Astronomical Extinction, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - B & C Spectograph, 1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - B Cor Boxc, 1936 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - BUC "B" Spectograph – 72 inch Equipment and Operation, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo (2 folders), 1970-1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo – Exposure Charts, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo Inter American Observatory 36 inch spectrograph, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo Observatory, 1968-1986 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo – Observing Records, 1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo Observing Program, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Cerro Tololo Observing - Yorka, 1983 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Codes, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Comets – Dr. Bob's Notes, 1974-1975 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Coordinate S-Systems, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Data Reduction Program Library, 1964 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - DTM Image Tube – 72 inch, 1966 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - DTM Image Tube Spectograph, 1980 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Eclipsic Binaries, 1956 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Emergencies, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Exposure charts, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Fan Shaped nebulae, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Flagstaff 72 inch exposure charts, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Flagstaff Calibration Sensitometer, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Flagstaff Darkroom, 1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Flagstaff – Observing Records, 1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Galactic Coordinates, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Globular Clusters Spectra, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Image Tube Project, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruction Manual Cassegrain Spectograph, 1973 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruments, 1982 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruments – Image Tubes, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruments – Light, 1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruments – Meteorological, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Instruments – Photometers, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Intensity Microphotometer, 1971-1986 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kaitchuck Secondaries, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kitt Peak Cerro Tololo – Users Committee, 1971-1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kitt Peak National Obs, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kitt Peak National Observatory: Cassegrain Spectograph, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kitt Peak National Observatory – Spectograph, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Kitt Peak Observing, 1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - La Plata Observatory – Argentina, 1966-1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Lantern Slides, 1951 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Las Campanas – Observing, 1989-1995 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Lick Observatory, 1981, 1982 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Lowell Observatory – Observatory Schedules, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Lowell Observatory Assistant, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Luminosity Functions, 1939 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Magellanic Clouds, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Microwave Radiation, 1945-1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mirrors – Aluminizing, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mirrors – Reflectivity, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Miscellaneous – Astronomical, 1931-1936 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Moon Photographs, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Moon, 1935, 1965 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mount Wilson & Palomar – Observing Records, 1964-1976 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - MT. Wilson Exposure Tests, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mt. Wilson – Miscellaneous Data, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mt. Wilson Observatory, 1978 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Mt. Wilson Observing, 1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Nebular Photometry Corrections, 1933 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Notation – Scientific, 1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories – Merida Venezuela, 1977-1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories – Argentina, 1966-1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories – Canada – David Dunlop, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories – Chile – Santiago, 1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Observatories – Colombia Bogota, 1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Office Equipment, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Old Exposure Chart, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Old Flagstaff Exposure Charts, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Old Observing Records, 1939 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Optical Instruments - Filters, 1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Palomar Exposure Charts, 1973-1975 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Palomar Observing, 1971-1976 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - PB Camera, 1954 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Perkins 69" Reflector- Lowell, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Perkins 72-inch Telescope, 1963-1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Perkins Sensitometer, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photoelectric Photometry, 1955 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Equipment, 1972-1988 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Films, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Characteristic Curves, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Cutting Machines, 1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates - Darkroom, 1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Defects, 1968 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Eastman Kodak Co., 1956-1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Efficiency, 1971 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Envelopes, 1973 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Mt. Wilson, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photographic Plates – Sensitization, 1965-1974 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photometric Tests-Perkins Observatory, 1946 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Photometric Classification of Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Planetary Nebulae, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Postal Rates, 1981 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Printers & Publishers, 1962-1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Publication Costs, 1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Radio Astronomy, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Radio Astronomy – Galactic Radiation OSU Data, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Reselection Nebulae, 1980 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Schott iend Telescopes, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Scientists, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Seeing Tests, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Selected Areas, 1936 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Short Investigations – Unpublished, 1935 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - South Galactic Pole, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs, 1955, 1980, 1985 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs – Design, 1941-1984 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs – Flagstaff, 1973-1980 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectograph Interference Bands, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs – Kitt Peak Cerro Tololo, 1967-1979 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs – Mt. Wilson 60 inch, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectographs – small, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectroscopic Binaries, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Spectroscopy – Spectrometry of Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Stars – Diameters, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Stars- Space Density, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Stellar Color Temperatures – Late Types, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Stellar Temperatures, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Stellar Temperatures & Colors, 1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Steward Observatory – Spectograph Speeds, 1971-1980 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Style Manuals, 1959, 1970 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Telescope Speeds, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Toronto, 1978 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Victoria – Dominion Observatory, 1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Victoria Observing, 1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Visual Binaries – Detection, 1976 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Visual Binaries – Spectra, 1987-1995 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Yc Camera, 1972 (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
    - Yoder Spectograph, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0007)
  - Miscellaneous Topics and Publications, 1928-1994
    - Bidelman Symposium, 1979-1988 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Chromosphere, 1934-1935 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Chromosphere Spectrum, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - CI Term Values, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Classification on 20 A/m Coude Plates Pd, Ced, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Curves of Growth, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - D-Lines (2 folders), 1960-1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - D-Lines (Harrington, 1963) Total Absorptions, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - D-Lines – Small Amplitude Variables, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - D-Line Tracings, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - External Galaxies – Spectra, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - External Galaxies – Surface Brightness, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - F-Values, 1955 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - F-Values – Oxygen, 1942 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - For Archives, 1950-1977 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Galactic Rotation, 1947-1954 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Galactic Structure, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Galactic Structure – Spiral Arms, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Intergalactic Matter, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Interstellar D-Lines – High Latitude, 1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Interstellar Early Type Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Interstellar D-Lines – Intensities, 1957 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Large Magellanic Cloud, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Line Intensities – Theory, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Lowell Observatory, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Magellanic Stream – Possible Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Meteorite Craters, 1946 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Meteorites, 1962 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Meteor Showers, 1967 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Meteors and Fireballs, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Mira Variables Interstellar D-Line Intensities, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts and Papers, 1939 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Molecular Dissociation Calculations – (Stanger), undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Photography of Sun, 1950-1954 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Publications (3 folders), 1928-1994 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R Cor – Bor – Wavelengths, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R Cor – Ce Plates, Measurements, 1955 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R Coronae Borealis, 1961 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB 200 inch PC, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB Enlargements, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB Manuscript, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB – Original Tables, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB Perkins Plates, 1950-1951 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB Reports, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - R CrB – Visual Pb, 1959 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Radiation Theory – Absorption Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Radiation Black Body Intensities, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Radition Theory – Emission Lines, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Red Shift, 1976 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Schock Tube Spectra, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Shock Waves, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Data, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Granules, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Filaments Spectral Types, 1951 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Monitoring Program, 1989 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Prominences, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Solar Temperature, 1937 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Spectra, 1952 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Spectra Helioscope, 1930, 1935 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Stellar Atmospheres: Turbulence, 1960 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Stellar D-Lines Early Type Stars, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Sun-Filters, undated (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Sunspots, 1988 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Sun Eclipses, 1963 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)
    - Tracings, 1961-1969 (Box UA.1995.0166.0008)